{
    "id": "817af75300dc405caeebc5409510a192",
    "title": "Determiners And Pronouns Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "ba0ec441a9fc454b880e5823fae56730",
            "title": "Determiners and Pronouns Quiz",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I couldn't answer ............................... questions.",
                    "description": "Use many with a plural noun use every with a singular noun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much",
                        "every"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I haven't got ............................. money.",
                    "description": "Much and any are possible here with somewhat different meanings. Money is uncountable so it cannot be used with many.",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many",
                        "any"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has so ............................... wealth.",
                    "description": "Wealth is uncountable use much with it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don't have ............................... interest in politics.",
                    "description": "Many is not an adverb. It cannot modify an adjective. Some is used in affirmative clauses. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "many",
                        "some"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You don't give me ............................ help.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "many",
                        "some"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Milk does not provide as .............................. nutrition as curd.",
                    "description": "Nutrition is an uncountable noun. Use much with it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I did ............................ work in ............................ time today.",
                    "description": "Less is the comparative form of little.",
                    "answers": [
                        "more, little",
                        "more, less",
                        "more, lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You hardly eat ..................................",
                    "description": "Hardly is a negative word. You hardly eat anything means the same as you eat nothing. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "anything",
                        "something",
                        "nothing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although I didn't know ............................. at the party, I had a good time.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "anyone",
                        "someone",
                        "no one"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You have ................................ problems than me.",
                    "description": "Use a comparative adjective before than. Fewer is the comparative form of few. It is used with plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "fewer",
                        "few",
                        "less",
                        "lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There isn’t …………………….. we can do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "many",
                        "any",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have got .............................. water if you are thirsty.",
                    "description": "Little means hardly any water. A little indicates a small quantity. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "a little",
                        "few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}